A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Directory of Graduates FA841
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Directory of Graduates
1959-1979, 1986, 1987, 1990-1992, 2000-2001
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University
Acheson, N. H.
Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
FA841
2 Box(es)
2 boxes.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be closed to research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment
Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be closed to researchers at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/Head of Reference.
File Plan note
Former Classification: I 462
Conditions Governing Access note
This collection is open for scholarly research.
Scope and Contents
Various lists were made to maintain a record of up-to-date activities and addresses of students who were graduates of The Rockefeller University. The form varied in the early years, but starting with 1972/1973 there appeared a greater regularity.
Arrangement
Arranged in chronological order. Alphabetical arrangement starting with 1966/1967.
Arboviruses; Cell and biomolecular sciences; Medicine, Preventive; Medical technology; Chemistry; Animal behavior; Biochemistry; Medical sciences; Life sciences; Biology -- Research; Medical education; Science -- Study and teaching; Medical research; Rockefeller University; Acheson, N. H.; Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
- "Present activities of 50 Graduates", 1959/1963 (Box 1)
  Arrangement note
  Arranged by type of appointment held.
- Alumni, 1964 October
  Arranged in alphabetical order.
  - 1964 October (Box 1)
  - 1966/1967 (Box 1)
  - 1967/1968 (Box 1)
  - 1968/1969 (Box 1)
  - 1969/1970 (Box 1)
  - 1970/1971 (Box 1)
  - 1971/1972 (Box 1)
  - 1972/1973 (Box 1)
    Scope and Contents note
    Published March 1973.
  - 1973 (Box 1)
    Published December 1973.
  - 1974 (Box 1)
    Published December 1974.
  - 1976 (Box 1)
  - 1977 (Box 1)
  - 1978 (Box 1)
  - 1979 (Box 1)
  - 1986 (Box 1)
  - 1987 (Box 1)
  - 1990 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 1991 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 1992 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 4)